export const FindExpertData = {
  Heading: "Find Experts with Related Skills",
  description:
    "Build your dream team by connecting with highly qualified professionals across diverse tech specialties",
  ChipsData: [
    {
      id: 1,
      labelName: "ASP Developers",
      labelHeading: "Bank IT",
      detail: [
        {
          Question: "How much does it cost to hire dedicated developers?",
          Answer:
            "Hiring dedicated developers' costs vary by location and expertise. US-based rates range from $70 to $130 per hour, while Europe-based developers may cost $5,000 to $25,000 per month."
        },
        {
          Question: "How long does it take to hire a remote developer?",
          Answer:
            "Hiring a remote developer typically takes 4-6 weeks due to screening for communication, cultural fit, and time zone compatibility"
        },
        {
          Question: "Is it hard to find a remote developer?",
          Answer:
            "Finding a remote developer can be challenging but not with CodersWire. Our streamlined process ensures quick access to skilled offshore developers within a week, tailored to your project needs."
        },
        {
          Question: "How do remote developers work?",
          Answer:
            "Remote developers in outsourcing software development provide services from a different location, offering flexibility, cost-efficiency, and collaboration through online platforms and tools."
        },
        {
          Question: "What is the process of hiring a developer?",
          Answer:
            "The process of hiring a developer involves initial screening, technical assessments, behavioral interviews, reference checks, client-specific evaluations, interviews, onboarding, and ongoing performance monitoring for project success and alignment."
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      labelName: "ADO Developers",
      labelHeading: "Bank IT",
      detail: [
        {
          Question: "How to find the best Developers for hire?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 6",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 7",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      labelName: "C++ Developers",
      labelHeading: "Bank IT",
      detail: [
        {
          Question: "How to find the best Developers for hire?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 2",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 3",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      labelName: "Full-Stack Developers",
      labelHeading: "Bank IT",
      detail: [
        {
          Question: "How to find the best Developers for hire?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 2",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 3",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      labelName: "Dedicated Developers",
      labelHeading: "Bank IT",
      detail: [
        {
          Question: "How to find the best Developers for hire?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 2",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 3",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      labelName: "C# Developers",
      labelHeading: "Bank IT",
      detail: [
        {
          Question: "How to find the best Developers for hire?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 2",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 3",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      labelName: "Core Developers",
      labelHeading: "Bank IT",
      detail: [
        {
          Question: "How to find the best Developers for hire?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 2",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 3",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      labelName: "VB Developers",
      labelHeading: "Bank IT",
      detail: [
        {
          Question: "How to find the best Developers for hire?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 2",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 3",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
        {
          Question: "What are the tools used by Developers?",
          Answer:
            "Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. 4",
        },
      ],
    },

  ],
};